https://www.ribeye.co.uk/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY & TERMS
Ribeye (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the www.ribeye.co.uk website (the “Service”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.
We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at www.ribeye.co.uk
Information Collection and Use
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number (“Personal Information”).
Log Data
We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyse this type of information in order to increase our Service’s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Behavioural Remarketing
Ribeye uses remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.
Types of data we collect:
Google AnalyticsWhen someone visits this website, we use Google’s Analytics service to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site, what devices they are using and what country they are from. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. We not only abide by this Privacy Policy, but comply with all applicable laws, policies and regulations relating to the collection of information by visitors.
Google AdWordsWe use the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on other websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who started but didn’t complete a purchase.Advertising to previous visitors could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using Google’s Ad Preferences page. If you really want to, you can opt out of targeted interest-based Google advertising entirely (although that does mean that you will see more ads for goods you aren’t interested in). You can read more on Google’s use of data collected via this link http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analysing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Explaining the Legal Basis for Processing Data
Consent – For example, when you tick a box to become a part of our Ribeye community.
Contractual Obligations – In certain circumstances, we need your personal data to comply with our contractual obligations. For example, if you require delivery we’ll collect your address details and pass them to our courier.
Legal compliance – If the law requires us to, we may need to collect and process your data. For example, we can pass on details of people involved in fraud or other criminal activity affecting the Company to law enforcement.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. As such we make no warranties as to the level of security afforded to your data, except that we will always act in accordance with the relevant UK and EU legislation.
International Transfer
Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United Kingdom and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United Kingdom and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
In the event that a dispute arises with regards to the international transfer of data, you agree that the courts of England and Wales shall have exclusive jurisdiction over the matter.
Data Retention Period
Whenever we collect or process your personal data, we’ll only keep it for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which is was collected. At the end of the retention period, your data will either be deleted completely or anonymised, for example by aggregation with other data so that it can be used in a non-identifiable way for statistical analysis and business planning.
E.g. Orders – When you place an order, we’ll keep the personal data you give us for five years so we can comply with our legal and contractual obligations including warranties.
Links to Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
How Can You Stop The Use Of Your Personal Data For Direct Marketing?
Click the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any email communication that we send you. We will then stop any further emails.
Contacting the Regulator
If you feel that your data has not been handled correctly, or you are unhappy with our response to any requests you have made to us regarding the use of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.
If you feel that your data has not been handled correctly, or you are unhappy with our response to any requests you have made to us regarding the use of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.
You can contact them by calling 0303 123 1113. Or you can go online to www.ico.org.uk/concerns (opens in a new window; please note we can’t be responsible for the content of external websites)
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Jurisdiction
This Policy shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of England and Wales, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us
Close
Enquire
What service are youinterested in?
Superyacht Tenders
Leisure Boats
Have a more general question?Get in touch with us on:
+44 (0)1803 832060
hello@ribeye.co.uk
Close
Make a leisure
boat enquiry
+44 (0)1803 832060
hello@ribeye.co.uk
Your details
First Name
Last Name
Email
Phone
Add these optional details so we can introduce you to the right member of our team
Interested in?
Any
A500
A550
A600
A683
A811
PRIME SIX19
PRIME SIX77
Any other info
Sorry, there were some problems with your information. Please check the highlighted fields are completed, and submit again.
Close
Make a tender
enquiry
+44 (0)1803 832060
superyacht@ribeye.co.uk
Your details
First Name
Last Name
Email
Phone
Add these optional details so we can introduce you to the right member of our team
Tender Size (Metres)
5
6
7
8
9
10
11
12
Any
Delivery Time (Months)
3
6
9
12
15
18
21
24
Any other info
Sorry, there were some problems with your information. Please check the highlighted fields are completed, and submit again.
Close
Make an approved
used enquiry
+44 (0)1803 832060
hello@ribeye.co.uk
Your details
First Name
Last Name
Email
Phone
Add these optional details so we can introduce you to the right member of our team
Interested in?
Model of Interest
Any other info
Sorry, there were some problems with your information. Please check the highlighted fields are completed, and submit again.
Close
RSVP Now
Your details
First Name
Last Name
Email
Phone
Interested in?
Any
A500
A550
A600
A683
A811
PRIME SIX19
PRIME SIX77
S785
Preferred Date:
Any
1 September 2020
2 September 2020
3 September 2020
4 September 2020
5 September 2020
6 September 2020
7 September 2020
30 September 2020
AM/PM appointment:
None
AM
PM
None
None
AM
PM
Any other info
Sorry, there were some problems with your information. Please check the highlighted fields are completed, and submit again.
Close
Thank you
Your message
has been sent
Thank you for enquiry. We are currently running our Ribeye Experience event throughout September which may delay our response to you. We will endeavour to get back to you within three business day. If you do not hear from us after this time please contact us at hello@ribeye.co.uk or +44 (0)1803 832060. We’d love to hear from you!
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We value your data privacy. Click ok to continue or learn more about our Privacy Policy.
Ok, I agree
